scraps123.com 2012-11-02

# Scraps123 Privacy Policy Status and Cover Pic

Your use of this website (www.scraps123.com) indicates your acceptance of this policy in it's entire form. Also, this privacy policy may be updated or changed at any time at our discretion, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. Your continued use of our website indicates your acceptance of any changes or updates. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site.  

 **Collection of Information -**

We collect personally identifiable information, like email addresses, ONLY when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request (for example to add you to our mailing lists).

 **Cookie/Tracking Technology -**  
We may collect personal information about your visit and your use of our website. This website may use cookies to track your internet activities and your preferences. Cookies allow website operators and 3rd party advertisers to identify you as a returning visitor and serve advertisements that are relevant to your internet preferences.

This website utilizes Google and their Adsense advertising system to serve ads to visitors on our website. Please note that -

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy. ](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

The advertising Vendor(s) may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

 **Commitment to Data Security -**

Your voluntarily submitted personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, and contractors like Google Feedburner, who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential, have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings
